martinmadsen software developer, me@martinbjeldbak.com

about

502/25 Walsh Street Milton 4064 Queensland Australia

26 years old +61 413 043 210 martinbjeldbak.com 7 / martinbjeldbak 7 martinbjeldbak

languages

bilingual Danish/English IELTS score: 8.0

programming

Ruby on Rails Heroku, AWS, SQL LATEX, HTML, Git JavaScript (ES6, React) OS X, Unix

interests

machine learning
TDD, functional
programming
service oriented
architecture
web development

experience

since 2016 **Back-end Software Developer & Project Manager**Ruby on Rails software developer working with our clients to build web-based systems across many different industries, from finance to flood mapping. I work on setting up infrastructure in AWS to building service objects in Rails and avoid-

ing circular dependencies.

2012-2014 **Student Software Developer** Falck Healthcare a/s, Aalborg, Denmark

Development of Ruby on Rails-based system used daily by ca. 40 of Falck's physiotherapists to journal their patients' treatments and wellbeing.

2010-2014 **Founder** Divambu (shut down)

Ran my own small company developing and hosting web sites for clients.

education

2014-2016 M.Sc. in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

Majoring in Computer Science (120 ECTS) Specializing in Machine Intelligence

2014-2015 **Studying abroad** University of California, San Diego

Fully accredited as part of the first year of my master's degree from Aalborg

University

2011-2014 **B.Sc.** in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

Majoring in Computer Science (180 ECTS)

2008-2011 Student EUC Nord - Technical Gymnasium of Hjørring

Focus in physics and engineering

other activities

2013-2014 **Student member of the Study Board** Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

Elected position. Handling of educations within Computer Science curricula at the university, quality assurance of education, handling of exemptions, etc.

projects

2015 **XQuery Processor** UC San Diego, **Q** / martinbjeldbak/xquery-processor

Implemented a subset of the XQuery and XPath XML query languages in Java

2016 A Hierarchical Tree Distance Measure for Classification martinbjeldbak.com/thesis.pdf

Concluded my M.Sc. degree. Published in Proceedings of the 6th International Conference on Pattern Recognition Applications and Methods - Volume

1: ICPRAM

...and many others! I contribute as much as I can to open source and work on other projects for fun. For more examples, feel free to check out my GitHub profile linked above.